

FURKAN KAPUKAYA

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a person who is open to self-development, aims to gain experience and benefit himself and the company he works for. I am a person who adapts to teamwork, is problem solving oriented, fast and does not give up, follows new technologies quickly, and tries to convey what he knows. I want to take responsibility in every field and show myself in the company where I have worked for many years.

EDUCATION

Anatolian University

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS | 2022 - NOW

Kirklareli University

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING | 2019 - 2021

- 3,55/4 AGNO
- Artificial Intelligence Workshop Volunteer
- I studied C#, Python, Java, PostgreSQL, PHP, HTML and CSS technologies at a basic level.

COMPUTER SKILLS

C# (Windows Forms - Web - Console)
.NET | .NET Core
ASP.NET (MVC - Layered Architecture)
SQL
HTML | CSS | BOOTSTRAP
GIT (Github)
MICROSOFT SQL SERVER
VISUAL STUDIO | VISUAL STUDIO CODE
POSTMAN
MICROSOFT OFFICE

HOBBIES



EXPERIENCES

Jr. Software Developer

PXL DIGITAL SOLUTIONS | AUGUST 2023 - NOW

 I am involved in the development and bug fixing of various projects within the company.

Jr. Software Developer

OFMARK.COM | FEBRUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2023

 Basic enhancements and bug fixing in Ofmark E-Commerce platform for end users and companies. I am working with PXL Digital Solutions.

Jr. Software Developer Intern

OMEGA BIGDATA I MARCH 2021 - JUNE 2021

 I took part in web projects created for new generation loyalty platforms for shoppers and employees. My task is to develop, edit and report web projects.

Volunteer

ÜNOG I JANUARY 2021

I volunteered for ÜNOG's GGJ21 event. Communicating one-on-one with the participants, etc. I completed the tasks. It was an enjoyable and educational experience.

PROJECTS

Github | Youtube | Portfolio Website

CERTIFICATES

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Version Control Systems and Portfolio | Git&Github

MVC Project Camp | PG1926 Programming Camp

Blockchain 101 | Cyber Security 101 | Online Safety Training



